[
    {
        "questionNo": "Q1",
        "question": "Which words make this statement true?<br> 74 ____ 72.",
        "options": [
            "is less than",
            "is greater than",
            "is equal to"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q2",
        "question": "Which words make this statement true?<br> 85 ____ 89.",
        "options": [
            "is less than",
            "is greater than",
            "is equal to"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q3",
        "question": "Which words make this statement true?<br> 47 ____ 47.",
        "options": [
            "is less than",
            "is greater than",
            "is equal to"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q4",
        "question": "Which words make this statement true?<br> 56 ____ 53.",
        "options": [
            "is less than",
            "is greater than",
            "is equal to"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q5",
        "question": "Which sign makes the statement true?<br> 28 ____ 18.",
        "options": [
            ">",
            "=",
            "<"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q6",
        "question": "Which sign makes the statement true?<br> 45 ____ 54.",
        "options": [
            ">",
            "=",
            "<"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q7",
        "question": "Put these numbers in order from greatest to least:<br> 11, 13, 96.",
        "options": [
            "13, 11, 96",
            "96, 13, 11",
            "11, 13, 96"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q8",
        "question": "Put these numbers in order from greatest to least:<br> 98, 45, 12.",
        "options": [
            "98, 45, 12",
            "45, 12, 98",
            "12, 98, 45"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q9",
        "question": "Put these numbers in order from least to greatest:<br> 81, 49, 13.",
        "options": [
            "49, 81, 13",
            "81, 49, 13",
            "13, 49, 81"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "questionNo": "Q10",
        "question": "Put these numbers in order from least to greatest:<br> 92, 36, 27.",
        "options": [
            "27, 36, 92",
            "36, 92, 27",
            "92, 27, 36"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    }
]
